wisestartupblog.com 2016-04-05

# Privacy Policy

Life Tailored is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors and users of this website and its related subscription service. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat and use the information we collect when you uselifetailored.com or sign up for our newsletter(s).

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. Life Tailored doesn’t collection any information except that expressly provide by you.

When using our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or phone number; we may also request additional information such as age, birth date, buying preferences, annual income or other demographic or profile information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

We may use any of the information we collect from you in one or more of the following ways:

  *  **To personalize your experience:**  Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  *  **To improve our website:**  We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  *  **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.**
  *  **To send periodic emails:  **The email address you provide may be used to send you occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### Usage Information

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, Life Tailored may gather anonymous information to analyse our site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. All of this information is collected to help us create a better, faster, more efficient website and provide you with better content. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

#### Use Of Cookies

Like most websites, Life Tailored may, from time to time, use the “cookies” feature of major browser applications. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s [hard drive](http://skimlinks.pgpartner.com/mrdr.php?url=http%3A%2F%2Fskimlinks.pgpartner.com%2Fsearch.php%2Fform_keyword%3Dhard%2Bdrive "Shopping Link Added by SkimWords") through your web browser (if you allow), enabling the site or its service provider to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about side traffic and site interaction so that we can learn which areas of our site are useful and provide you with the best possible service. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our Site.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third Party Links

In order to offer the best possible information, Life Tailored will often include or offer third party products, links or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Third Party Advertising

Occasionally you may receive an email marked “Dedicated Email” in the subject line and email header. These emails are not necessarily reflective of the opinions of our editorial staff. They are content paid for by our sponsors. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service in a Dedicated Email should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are a general audience site. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years or older. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Modifications

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 22 May 2010.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, about this site, or you would like to have us remove your information from our records, please contact us at hello@wisestartupblog.com.
